First of all, thank you. You helped me turn my senior design project at college into my business.
It's my second year in business. Last year we did $150,000 and I want to get to $500,000.
We do digital business cards for primarily in real estate. What do you think?
You want to grow this?
I'm not trying to sell. I just want to make money and then sell more expensive things later.
Right now, I'm just using this to make money.
To make money?
Yes.
Dude, I think if you sold something else, you'd make way more money.
I agree.
Okay.
Like what you have is a hard pitch because I'd be like, here's my Instagram.
That's my digital business card. If you want to find out more about me, watch some content.
You obviously have the skill of sales.
And so I'd rather just like use that on a better opportunity vehicle.
Got it.
This world is just crumbling.
You want to hire me?
Throw in a real note though.
Oh, that wasn't real? That's not a real offer.
All right.
Neither was mine.
Two can play that game.
I don't know what I'm doing.
What do I do in the meantime to make money?
You're able to, you know, shake hands and kiss babies and close.
And so like you can pretty much just like go look at any business that exists and just do that and probably make way more money.
Like you start a lawn care business tomorrow, like knocking door to door and probably get to two or three million dollars a year.
You could sell solar and make, you know, 800 grand a year on your own just with your existing skillset.
Got it. Thank you, Alex.